Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Course Bulletins MC.286
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Collection of Course Bulletins
1832-2017
New York University Archives
New York University
MC.286
130 Linear Feet in 378 bound volumes and 195 boxes
0.34 Gigabytes
The collection consists of publications (bulletins, catalogs, announcements, etc.) that outline the course of study at New York University and its component schools, dating from 1832 to 2017. The publications are a mix of bound and unbound materials, as well as electronic records in the PDF format. They typically include an overview of the school, degree requirements, lists of faculty and administrators, and course descriptions. Early publications sometimes include lists of students and degrees conferred.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Existence and Location of Copies
Additional duplicate copies of publications are held in the collection of New York University Publications (preservation copies) (RG 1.0).
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; provenance is unknown. Material from 2020 accretion was donated by Richard Carreno in July 2019. The accession number associated with this donation is 2020.003.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into series based on the New York University Archives's record group classification system. Titles for the record groups are based on the school or program's current official name (as of 2019). For example, School of Commerce bulletins are included as part of the Stern School of Business record group.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of publications (bulletins, catalogs, announcements, etc.) that outline the course of study at New York University and its component schools, dating from 1832 to 2017. The publications are a mix of bound and unbound materials, as well as electronic records in the PDF format. They typically include an overview of the school, degree requirements, lists of faculty and administrators, and course descriptions. Early publications sometimes include lists of students and degrees conferred.
Education, Higher.
- All University (RG 1), 1832-1978
  - Catalogues, circulars, and related material, 1832-1854 (Box 1)
  - Catalogues, circulars, and related material, 1836, 1839-1849, 1851-1854, 1856-1857, 1859-1865 (Box 195)
  - Catalogues, 1854-1881 (Box 2)
  - Catalogues, 1881-1888 (Box 3)
  - Catalogues, 1888-1892 (Box 4)
  - Catalogues, 1892-1894, 1913-1917 (Box 5)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes Department of English (1914-1915) and Modern Language Group (1916-1917)
  - Catalogue, 1840-1841 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue, 1846-1847 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue, 1848-1850 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue, 1858-1859 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue, 1861-1875 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1863-1864 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue, 1868-1869 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue, 1870-1871 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue, 1875-1876 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue, 1877-1881 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue, 1878-1879 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue, 1881-1882 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1885-1886 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1886-1887 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1887-1888 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1888-1889 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1889-1890 (Box 186)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (3 Copies), 1890-1891 (Box 187)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1891-1892 (Box 187)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1892-1893 (Box 187)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1893-1894 (Box 187)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1894-1895 (Box 187)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1895-1896 (Box 187)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1896-1897 (Box 187)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1897-1898 (Box 187)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (3 Copies), 1898-1899 (Box 187)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1899-1900 (Box 187)
  - Announcements and Sixty-Eighth Commenecement Program, 1900-1901 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1900-1901)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (3 Copies), 1900-1901 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1900-1901)
  - Bi-Weekly Bulletin (Vol I. No. 1), February 1901 (Box 178)
  - Bi-Weekly Bulletins (Bound Volumes I-IV), 1901-1905 (Box 193)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 Copies), 1901-1902 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1901-1902)
  - General University Catalogue (Vol. II No. 2), February 1902 (Box 178)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 copies), 1902-1903 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1902-1903)
  - Bi-Weekly Bulletin (Vol. IV No. 1), January 1903 (Box 178)
  - General University Catalogue (Vol. III No. 1), January 1903 (Box 178)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 copies), 1903-1904 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1903-1904)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 copies), 1904-1905 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1904-1905)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1904-1906 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1904-1906)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 copies), 1905-1906 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1905-1906)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (3 Copies), 1906-1907 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1906-1907)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 copies), 1907-1908 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1907-1908)
  - Catalogue and Announcements (2 copies), 1908-1909 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1908-1909)
  - Catalogue, 1909-1910 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1909-1910)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1910-1911 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1910-1911)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1911-1912 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1911-1912)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1912-1913 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1912-1913)
  - Catalogue (3 Copies), 1913-1914 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1913-1914)
  - Announcements, 1914 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1914)
    Includes announcements for study abroad programs and an assortment of other courses.
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1914-1915 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1914-1915)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1915-1916 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1915-1916)
  - Catalogue (3 Copies), 1916-1917 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1916-1917)
  - Announcement of the Modern Language Group, 1916-1917 (Box 5)
  - Catalogue (3 Copies), 1917-1918 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1917-1918)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1918-1919 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1918-1919)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1919-1920 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1919-1920)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1920-1921 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1920-1921)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1921-1922 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1921-1922)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1922-1923 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1922-1923)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1923-1924 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1923-1924)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1924-1925 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1924-1925)
  - Catalogue (3 Copies), 1925-1926 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1925-1926)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1926-1927 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1926-1927)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1927-1928 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1927-1928)
  - Catalogue (2 Copies), 1928-1929 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1928-1929)
  - An Index of Courses Offered at NYU, 1928-1929 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound Index 1928-1929)
  - An Index of Courses Offered at NYU, 1929-1930 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound Index 1929-1930)
  - Catalogue (2 copies), 1929-1930 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1929-1930)
  - Catalogue, 1930-1931 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1931-1932 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1932-1933 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1933-1934 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1934-1935 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1935-1936 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1936-1937 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1937-1938 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1938-1939 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1939-1940 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1940-1941 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1941-1942 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1942-1943 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1944-1945 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1945-1946 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1946-1947 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1947-1948 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue (3 copies), 1948-1949 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1948-1949)
  - Catalogue (4 copies), 1949-1950 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1949-1950)
  - Catalogue (4 copies), 1950-1951 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1950-1951)
  - Catalogue (3 copies), 1951-1952 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1951-1952)
  - General Information, 1955 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1955)
  - General Information, 1957 (Volume RG1 Bulletins - Bound 1957)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1964 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1964 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1964 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1965 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1965 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1965 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1966 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1966 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1966 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1967 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1967 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1967 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1968 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1968 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1969 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1969 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1969 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1970 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1970 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 3 (2 copies), 1970 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 4, 1970 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1971 (Box 176)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1971 (Box 176)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1971 (Box 176)
  - Bulletin, 1971-1974 (Box 177)
  - Bulletin (2 copies), 1972-1973 (Box 176)
  - Bulletin (School of Education), 1973-1974 (Box 176)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1974 (Box 177)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1974 (Box 177)
  - Bulletin, 1975-1976 (Box 177)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1976 (Box 177)
  - Bulletin - Part 2 (2 copies), 1976 (Box 177, Box 178)
  - Bulletin, 1977-1978 (Box 178)
- Sunrise Semester (RG 7.3.1.1), 1961-1982
  - Bulletins, 1961-1982 (Box 6)
- Institute of Afro-American Affairs (RG 9.8), 1968-1974
  - Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
- Summer School (RG 16), 1895-2003
  - Bulletins and announcements, 1895-1898, 1900-1912 (Box 7)
  - Bulletins, 1897-1915 (Box 8)
  - Bulletins, 1916-1931 (Box 9)
  - Announcements, flyers, and other ephemera, 1912-1937 (Box 10)
  - Bulletins, 1924-1931 (Volume RG16 Bulletins - Bound 1924-1931)
  - Summer School - Department of Music Education bulletins, 1925-1934 (Box 178)
  - Bulletins, 1932-1939 (Volume RG16 Bulletins - Bound 1932-1939)
  - Bulletins, 1940-1946 (Volume RG16 Bulletins - Bound 1940-1946)
  - Bulletins, 1947-1948, 1952-1956, 1960-1965 (Box 11)
  - Bulletins, 1955-1962 (Volume RG16 Bulletins - Bound 1955-1962 c.1)
  - Bulletins, 1955-1962 (Volume RG16 Bulletins - Bound 1955-1962 c.2)
  - Bulletins, 1966-1968 (Box 12)
  - Bulletins, 1969-1971 (Box 13)
  - Bulletins, 1971-1973 (Box 14)
  - Bulletins, 1974-1976 (Box 15)
  - Bulletins, 1977-1983 (Box 16)
  - Bulletins, 1984-1988 (Box 17)
  - Bulletins, 1989-1994 (Box 18)
  - Bulletins, 1995-2000 (Box 19)
  - Bulletins, 2001-2003 (Box 20)
  - Summer School - Department of Music Education bulletins, 1925-1934 (Box 178)
- University College of Arts and Science (University Heights) (RG 18), 1893-1973
  - Bulletins, 1893-1901 (Volume RG18 Bulletins - Bound 1893-1901)
  - Bulletins and announcements, 1900-1904, 1914-1943, 1954-1957 (Box 21)
    Includes Havenmeyer Chemical Laboratory courses (1904).
  - Bulletins, 1901-1913 (Volume RG18 Bulletins - Bound 1901-1913)
  - Bulletins, 1913-1925 (Volume RG18 Bulletins - Bound 1913-1925)
  - Bulletins, 1925-1931 (Volume RG18 Bulletins - Bound 1925-1931)
  - Bulletins, 1931-1937 (Volume RG18 Bulletins - Bound 1931-1937)
  - Bulletins, 1932-1940 (Volume RG18 Bulletins - Bound 1932-1940)
  - Bulletins, 1940-1949 (Volume RG18 Bulletins - Bound 1940-1949)
  - Bulletins, 1949-1958 (Volume RG18 Bulletins - Bound 1949-1958)
  - Bulletins, 1958-1963 (Volume RG18 Bulletins - Bound 1958-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1966 (Volume RG18 Bulletins - Bound 1963-1966)
  - Bulletins, 1957-1973 (Box 22)
- College of Arts and Science (Washington Square) (RG 19), 1903-2016
  - Bulletins, 1903-1914 (Volume RG19 Bulletins - Bound 1903-1914)
  - Bulletins, 1911-1941, 1952, 1959-1960 (Box 23)
    Includes Evening Division.
  - Bulletins, 1914-1925 (Volume RG19 Bulletins - Bound 1914-1925)
  - Bulletins, 1925-1935 (Volume RG19 Bulletins - Bound 1925-1935)
  - Bulletins, 1935-1941 (Volume RG19 Bulletins - Bound 1935-1941)
  - Bulletins, 1941-1947 (Volume RG19 Bulletins - Bound 1941-1947)
  - Bulletins, 1947-1953 (Volume RG19 Bulletins - Bound 1947-1953)
  - Bulletins, 1953-1960 (Volume RG19 Bulletins - Bound 1953-1960)
  - Bulletins, 1960-1967 (Volume RG19 Bulletins - Bound 1960-1967)
  - Bulletins, 1961-1964, 1966-1967 (Box 24)
  - Bulletins, 1967-1976 (Box 25)
  - Bulletins, 1976-1981 (Box 26)
  - Bulletins, 1981-1985 (Box 27)
  - Bulletins, 1986-1990 (Box 28)
  - Bulletins, 1991-1996 (Box 29)
  - Bulletins, 1996-2000 (Box 30)
  - Bulletins, 2000-2008 (Box 31)
  - Bulletins, 2008-2012 (Box 32)
  - Bulletins, 2012-2016 (Box 33)
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 2000-2016 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- Evening College of Arts and Science (RG 19.3), 1965-1968
  - Bulletins, 1965-1968 (Box 172)
- Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (RG 20), 1885-2017
  - Bulletins, 1885-1901 (Volume RG20 Bulletins - Bound 1885-1901)
  - Bulletins, announcements, and related items, 1886-1887, 1900-1902, 1906-1907, 1911, 1933-1934,1936-1941 (Box 34)
    Includes Department of Classics "The Excavations of Tell Ajjul" (1932-1933)
  - Bulletins, 1901-1912 (Volume RG20 Bulletins - Bound 1901-1912)
  - Bulletins, 1913-1918 (Volume RG20 Bulletins - Bound 1913-1918)
  - Bulletins, 1921-1930 (Volume RG20 Bulletins - Bound 1921-1930)
  - Bulletins, 1930-1937 (Volume RG20 Bulletins - Bound 1930-1937)
  - Bulletins, 1937-1942 (Volume RG20 Bulletins - Bound 1937-1942)
  - Bulletins, 1942-1948 (Volume RG20 Bulletins - Bound 1942-1948)
  - Bulletins, 1947-1967 (Box 35)
  - Bulletins, 1948-1953 (Volume RG20 Bulletins - Bound 1948-1953)
  - Bulletins, 1953-1957 (Volume RG20 Bulletins - Bound 1953-1957)
  - Bulletins, 1957-1962 (Volume RG20 Bulletins - Bound 1957-1962)
  - Bulletins, 1962-1967 (Volume RG20 Bound 1962-1967)
  - Bulletins, 1967-1974 (Box 36)
  - Bulletins, 1974-1976 (Box 37)
  - Bulletins, 1976-1982 (Box 38)
  - Bulletins, 1982-1990 (Box 39)
  - Bulletins, 1990-1996 (Box 40)
  - Bulletins, 1996-2001 (Box 41)
  - Bulletins, 2001-2005, 2009-2011 (Box 42)
    Includes Applications for Admission and Financial Aid (2003-2005).
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 2001-2017 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- Institute of Fine Arts (RG 20.1), 1923-2016
  - Bulletins, 1923-1924, 1926-1929, 1935-1942, 1944-1945, 1954-1968 (Box 43)
    Includes Department of Fine Arts.
  - Bulletins, 1968-1978 (Box 44)
  - Bulletins, 1979-1991 (Box 45)
  - Bulletins, 1991-2001 (Box 46)
  - Bulletins, 2007-2009, 2010-2011 (Box 47)
  - Previously Taught Courses in the History of Art and Archaeology 2005-2015 (PDF) (E-records Box - MC 286)
  - History of Art and Archaeology Courses (PDFs), 2015-2016 (E-records Box - MC 286)
  - Previously Taught Courses in Conservation 2005-2015 (PDF) (E-records Box - MC 286)
  - Conservation Courses (PDFs), 2015-2016 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences (RG 20.2), 1965-1987
  - Bulletins, 1965-1975, 1980-1983 (Box 48)
    Includes Graduate Program in Computer Science bulletin (1982).
  - Bulletins, 1985-1987 (Box 49)
- Liberal Studies Program (Graduate School) (RG 20.8), 1989-1990
  - Bulletins, 1989-1990 (Box 50)
- NYU/Manhattanville College (RG 20.10), 1978-1982
  - Bulletins, 1978-1982 (Box 50)
- New York College of Music (RG 21.8), 1899-1930
  - Bulletins, 1899-1930 (Box 51)
- Liberal Education Program (RG 21.29), 1981-1984
  - Bulletins, 1981-1984 (Box 52)
- Study Abroad Programs (RG 21.39), 1960-2005
  - NYU in Spain bulletins, 1960-1961, 1963-1971, 1973-1977, 1979-1981, 1987-1989 (Box 53)
  - Junior Year in Brazil bulletins, 1961-1964 (Box 53)
  - NYU in France bulletins, 1974-1977, 1985-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 53)
  - NYU in France bulletins, 1983-1985, 1996-1997 (Box 54)
  - NYU in London bulletins, 1978-1980, 1982, 1988-1989 (Box 54)
  - Bulletins, 1995, 1997, 1999-2005 (Box 54)
- Liberal Studies Program (RG 21.47), circa 2004-2015
  - Bulletin, circa 2004-2006, 2007-2009 (Box 55)
    Includes General Studies Program curriculum (circa 2004-2006).
  - Bulletins (PDFs), circa 2004-2006, 2009-2015 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- School of Law (RG 22), 1838-1989
  - Bulletins, 1838, 1858-1860, 1866, 1870-1875, 1878-1879, 1882-1886, 1891-1892, 1894-1904 (Box 56)
  - Bulletins, 1900-1924 (Volume RG22 Bulletins- Bound 1900-1924)
  - Bulletins, 1924-1938 (Volume RG22 Bulletins- Bound 1924-1938)
  - Bulletins, 1924-1945 (Volume RG22 Bulletins- Bound 1924-1945)
  - Bulletins, 1916-1919, 1928-1944, 1946-1959 (Box 57)
    Includes schedule of lectures (1928-1939).
  - Bulletins, 1938-1948 (Volume RG22 Bulletins- Bound 1938-1948)
  - Bulletins, 1949-1959 (Volume RG22 Bulletins- Bound 1949-1959)
  - Bulletins, 1951-1963 (Volume RG22 Bulletins- Bound 1951-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1959-1969 (Volume RG22 Bulletins- Bound 1959-1969)
  - Bulletins, 1959-1976 (Box 58)
  - Bulletins, 1976-1981, 1987-1989 (Box 59)
- Women's Law Class (RG 22.1), 1901-1924
  - Bulletins, 1915-1916 (Box 60)
- School of Law Graduate Division (RG 22.5), 1916-1998
  - Bulletins, 1916-1917, 1941-1942, 1945-1946, 1951-1972 (Box 61)
  - Bulletins, 1981-1998 (Box 62)
- School of Law Juris Doctor Program (RG 22.11), 1981-1993
  - Bulletins, 1981-1993 (Box 63)
- Institute for Law and Society (RG 22.13), 1993-circa 1999
  - Bulletins, 1993-circa 1999 (Box 63)
- School of Medicine (RG 23), 1841-2014
  - Bulletins, 1841-1881 (Box 64)
  - Bulletins, 1841-1844, 1846-1847, 1855-1856, 1858-1859, 1863-1865, 1870-1898 (Box 65)
  - Bulletins, 1883-1898 (Volume RG23 Bulletins - Bound 1883-1898)
  - Bulletins, 1898-1910 (Volume RG23 Bulletins - Bound 1898-1910)
  - Bulletins, 1900-1931 (Box 66)
  - Bulletins, 1910-1917 (Volume RG23 Bulletins - Bound 1910-1917)
  - Bulletins, 1920-1930 (Volume RG23 Bulletins - Bound 1920-1930)
  - Bulletins, 1930-1939 (Volume RG23 Bulletins - Bound 1930-1939)
  - Bulletins, 1931-1940 (Box 67)
  - Bulletins, 1939-1948 (Volume RG23 Bulletins - Bound 1939-1948)
  - Bulletins, 1940-1950, 1955-1956, 1958-1961 (Box 68)
  - Bulletins, 1948-1958 (Volume RG23 Bulletins - Bound 1948-1958)
  - Bulletins, 1958-1963 (Volume RG23 Bulletins - Bound 1958-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1961-1963, 1979-1985 (Box 69)
  - Bulletins, 1985-1993, 1999-2003, 2005-2006, 2008-2010 (Box 70)
  - Bulletin (PDF), 2012-2014 (E-records Box - MC 286)
- Post Graduate Medical School (RG 23.2), 1946-1979
  - Bulletins, 1946-1952 (Volume RG23.2 Bulletins - Bound 1946-1952)
  - Bulletins, 1952-1955 (Volume RG23.2 Bulletins - Bound 1952-1955)
  - Bulletins, 1956-1963 (Volume RG23.2 Bulletins - Bound 1956-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1948-1949, 1959-1968 (Box 71)
  - Bulletins, 1968-1974 (Box 72)
  - Bulletins, 1974-1979 (Box 73)
- Bellevue Hospital Medical College (RG 23.6), 1861-1920
  - Bulletins, 1861-1898, 1915, 1919-1920 (Box 74)
- Veterinary College (RG 23.8), 1900-1923
  - Bulletins, 1900-1923 (Box 178)
- School of Engineering and Science (RG 24), 1890-1972
  - Bulletins, 1890-1908 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1890-1908)
  - Bulletins, 1892-1908 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1892-1908)
  - Bulletins, 1895-1896, 1900-1901, 1913, 1915-1920, 1924-1941, 1943, 1959-1964 (Box 75)
    Includes War Training Courses (1943).
  - Bulletins, 1900-1911 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1900-1911)
  - Bulletins, 1909-1919 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1909-1919)
  - Bulletins, 1912-1925 (Box 188)
  - Bulletins, 1919-1928 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1919-1928)
  - Bulletins, 1921-1926 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1921-1926)
  - Programs, 1921-1932 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound Programs 1921-1932)
  - Bulletins, 1925-1932 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1925-1932)
  - Bulletins, 1926-1931 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1926-1931)
  - Bulletins, 1929-1935 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1929-1935)
  - Programs, 1931-1937 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound Programs 1931-1937)
  - Bulletins, 1931-1937 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1931-1937)
  - Bulletins, 1931-1940 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1931-1940)
  - Bulletins, 1936-1943 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1936-1943)
  - Bulletins, 1937-1942 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1937-1942)
  - Bulletins, 1937-1943 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1937-1943)
  - Bulletins, 1940-1948 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1940-1948)
  - Bulletins, 1943-1951 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1943-1951)
  - Bulletins, 1948-1952 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1948-1952)
  - Bulletins, 1951-1958 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1951-1958)
  - Bulletins, 1953-1957 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1953-1957)
  - Bulletins, 1959-1962 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1959-1962)
  - Bulletins, 1958-1963 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1958-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1967 (Volume RG24 Bulletins - Bound 1963-1967)
  - Bulletins, 1967-1972 (Box 76)
  - Bulletins (Evening Division), 1922, 1926-1932, 1935-1941, 1950, 1954, 1961-1962 (Box 77)
  - Bulletins (Graduate Division), 1937-1941, 1959-1964 (Box 78)
  - Bulletins (Graduate Division), 1940-1948 (Box RG24 Bulletins Grad - Bound 1940-1948)
  - Bulletins (Graduate Division), 1948-1957 (Box RG24 Bulletins Grad - Bound 1948-1957)
  - Bulletins (Graduate Division), 1957-1963 (Box RG24 Bulletins Grad - Bound 1957-1963)
  - Bulletins (Graduate Division), 1963-1967 (Box RG24 Bulletins Grad - Bound 1963-1967)
  - Bulletins (Graduate Division), 1967-1972 (Box 79)
- College of Dentistry (RG 25), 1865-1984
  - Bulletins, 1865-1893, 1896-1899, 1907-1912, 1914-1915, 1920-1921, 1924-1936 (Box 80)
  - Bulletins, 1865-1888 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1865-1888)
  - Bulletins, 1867-1896 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1867-1896)
  - Bulletins, 1887-1900 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1887-1900)
  - Bulletins, 1896-1903 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1896-1903)
  - Bulletins, 1899-1910 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1899-1910)
  - Bulletins, 1899-1914 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1899-1914)
  - Bulletins, 1903-1910 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1903-1910)
  - Bulletins, 1910-1915 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1910-1915)
  - Bulletins, 1910-1918 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1910-1918)
  - Bulletins, 1915-1920 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1915-1920)
  - Bulletins, 1918-1925 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1918-1925)
  - Bulletins, 1920-1925 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1920-1925)
  - Bulletins, 1925-1930 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1925-1930)
  - Bulletins, 1925-1943 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1925-1943)
  - Bulletins, 1936-1939, 1942-1943, 1948-1957 (Box 81)
  - Bulletins, 1936-1949 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1936-1949)
  - Bulletins, 1937-1940 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1937-1940)
  - Bulletins, 1940-1943 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1940-1943)
  - Bulletins, 1942-1951 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1942-1951)
  - Bulletins, 1948-1951 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1948-1951)
  - Bulletins, 1953-1958 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1953-1958)
  - Bulletins, 1957-1963 (Box 82)
  - Bulletins, 1958-1963 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1958-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1967 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1963-1967)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1971 (Box 83)
  - Bulletins, 1968-1973 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1968-1973)
  - Bulletins, 1971-1982 (Box 84)
  - Bulletins, 1973-1976 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1973-1976)
  - Bulletins, 1982-1987 (Box 85)
  - Bulletins, 1987-2010 (Box 86)
  - Pre-doctoral curriculums, 1978-1984 (Box 87)
- College of Dentistry - Post-Graduate Division (RG 25.1), 1926-2002
  - Bulletins, 1926-1932, 1934-1943, 1947-1956, 1957-1959 (Box 88)
  - Bulletins, 1959-1978, 1988-1990, 2002 (Box 89)
- Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development (RG 26), 1888-2015
  - Bulletins, 1888-1891, 1901-1905, 1914-1915 (Box 90)